{"sid": "ZLQPORSFC1YB_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 342872, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 342872, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 350389]], "time_left_end": "293", "answered_time": 350389, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "293", "question_time_start": 350390, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["calc_2", 353256], ["calc_8", 354010], ["calc_+", 354566], ["calc_1", 355256], ["calc_7", 355840], ["calc_=", 356733], ["submit", 361790]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "282", "answered_time": 361790, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "282", "question_time_start": 361790, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["calc_7", 367456], ["calc_7", 367640], ["calc_+", 368558], ["calc_8", 369489], ["calc_+", 370443], ["calc_9", 371010], ["calc_8", 371423], ["calc_=", 372256], ["submit", 376855]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 376855, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 376855, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["calc_7", 379622], ["calc_8", 380325], ["calc_+", 382264], ["calc_6", 384632], ["calc_0", 385340], ["calc_+", 386588], ["calc_4", 387361], ["calc_7", 387822], ["calc_=", 388376], ["submit", 393106]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "250", "answered_time": 393106, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "250", "question_time_start": 393107, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 399175]], "time_left_end": "244", "answered_time": 399175, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "244", "question_time_start": 399175, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 404990]], "time_left_end": "238", "answered_time": 404990, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "238", "question_time_start": 404990, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 410406]], "time_left_end": "233", "answered_time": 410406, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "233", "question_time_start": 410406, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 413691]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 413691, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 413692, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 420893]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 420893, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 420894, "question": "26+46", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 424405]], "time_left_end": "219", "answered_time": 424405, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 424405, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "219", "question_time_start": 424405, "question": "33+886", "correct_answer": 919, "events": [["submit", 431692]], "time_left_end": "212", "answered_time": 431692, "user_answer": "919", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "212", "question_time_start": 431693, "question": "7+86+84", "correct_answer": 177, "events": [["submit", 435204]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 435204, "user_answer": "177", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 435204, "question": "89+87", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 441021]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 441021, "user_answer": "186", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 441021, "question": "8+8+4+76", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 445321]], "time_left_end": "198", "answered_time": 445321, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "198", "question_time_start": 445321, "question": "7+59+37", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["calc_6", 451080], ["calc_6", 451273], ["calc_+", 451880], ["calc_3", 452493], ["calc_7", 453120], ["calc_=", 453748], ["submit", 458343]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "185", "answered_time": 458343, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "185", "question_time_start": 458344, "question": "4+4+8+14", "correct_answer": 30, "events": [["submit", 463948]], "time_left_end": "179", "answered_time": 463948, "user_answer": "30", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "179", "question_time_start": 463948, "question": "8+37+66", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 472521]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 472521, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 472522, "question": "54+646", "correct_answer": 700, "events": [["submit", 478397]], "time_left_end": "165", "answered_time": 478397, "user_answer": "700", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "165", "question_time_start": 478398, "question": "56+97+89+59", "correct_answer": 301, "events": [["calc_5", 482297], ["calc_6", 482704], ["calc_+", 483513], ["calc_9", 484528], ["calc_7", 485486], ["calc_+", 486281], ["calc_8", 486958], ["calc_9", 487537], ["calc_+", 488293], ["calc_5", 488987], ["calc_9", 489764], ["calc_=", 490411], ["submit", 495114]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 495114, "user_answer": "301", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 495114, "question": "69+39", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 499501]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 499501, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 499501, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 499501, "question": "4+77+47", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 506922]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 506922, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 506922, "question": "8+6+9+86", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 513337]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 513337, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 513337, "question": "17+694", "correct_answer": 711, "events": [["submit", 523429]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 523429, "user_answer": "711", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 523430, "question": "6+38+88", "correct_answer": 132, "events": [["submit", 541404]], "time_left_end": "102", "answered_time": 541404, "user_answer": "132", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "102", "question_time_start": 541404, "question": "68+23", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 544569]], "time_left_end": "99", "answered_time": 544569, "user_answer": "91", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "99", "question_time_start": 544569, "question": "59+49+48+63", "correct_answer": 219, "events": [["submit", 563070]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 563070, "user_answer": "219", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 563070, "question": "99+463", "correct_answer": 562, "events": [["submit", 570653]], "time_left_end": "73", "answered_time": 570653, "user_answer": "562", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "73", "question_time_start": 570653, "question": "6+26+27", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 576453]], "time_left_end": "67", "answered_time": 576453, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "67", "question_time_start": 576453, "question": "4+8+4+56", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 580023]], "time_left_end": "63", "answered_time": 580023, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "63", "question_time_start": 580024, "question": "67+66", "correct_answer": 133, "events": [["submit", 584903]], "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 584903, "user_answer": "133", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 584903, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 584903, "question": "7+4+4+86", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["submit", 590153]], "time_left_end": "53", "answered_time": 590152, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "53", "question_time_start": 590153, "question": "3+76+78", "correct_answer": 157, "events": [["submit", 596020]], "time_left_end": "47", "answered_time": 596020, "user_answer": "157", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "47", "question_time_start": 596020, "question": "87+478", "correct_answer": 565, "events": [["submit", 603317]], "time_left_end": "40", "answered_time": 603317, "user_answer": "565", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "40", "question_time_start": 603318, "question": "7+37+44", "correct_answer": 88, "events": [["submit", 607169]], "time_left_end": "36", "answered_time": 607169, "user_answer": "88", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "36", "question_time_start": 607169, "question": "9+69+39", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 615976]], "time_left_end": "27", "answered_time": 615976, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "27", "question_time_start": 615977, "question": "7+8+7+17", "correct_answer": 39, "events": [["submit", 621618]], "time_left_end": "22", "answered_time": 621618, "user_answer": "39", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "22", "question_time_start": 621618, "question": "63+69+94+76", "correct_answer": 302, "events": []}}}}}